在暗黑中寻找我的路
Feeling my way through the darkness
让跃动的心领导
Guided by a beating heart
我说不出哪里是这趟旅行的终点
I can’t tell where the journey will end
但我知道这是在哪里开始的
But I know where it starts
他们告诉我，我不懂，因为太年轻
They tell me I’m too young to understand
他们告诉我，我已迷失在梦中
They say I’m caught up in a dream
若我不苏醒，时间便会擦身而过
Well life will pass me by if I don’t open up my eyes
好吧，我已经找到它了
Well that’s fine by me
所以当这一切结束时，请叫醒我
So wake me up when it’s all over
当我长大，更有智慧了
When I’m wiser and I’m older
我总是在寻找自己
All this time I was finding myself
而且我并不知道我曾迷失过
And I didn’t know I was lost
所以当这一切结束时，请叫醒我
So wake me up when it’s all over
当我长大，更有智慧了
When I’m wiser and I’m older
我总是在寻找自己
All thistime I was finding myself
而且我并不知道我曾迷失过
And I didn’t know I was lost
我尝试顶住全世界的压力
I tried carrying the weight of the world
却无能为力
But I only have two hands
我希望拥有环游世界的机会
I hope I get the chance to travel the world
毫无计划
And I don’t have any plans
我奢望永生不老
I wish that I could stay forever this young
不惧死亡
Not afraid to close my eyes
生活就是上帝给众生制造的一场游戏
Life’s a game made for everyone
以爱为代价
And love is a prize
所以当这一切结束时，请叫醒我
So wake me up when it’s all over
当我长大，更有智慧了
When I’m wiser and I’m older
我总是在寻找自己
All this time I was finding myself
而且我并不知道我曾迷失过
And I didn’t know I was lost
所以当这一切结束时，请叫醒我
So wake me up when it’s all over
当我长大，更有智慧了
When I’m wiser and I’m older
我总是在寻找自己
All this time I was finding myself
而且我并不知道我曾迷失过
And I didn’t know I was lost
By TD